our planet is full of places in the
deepest corners of the most forgotten
regions of this world that will fill your
spirit with all and leave you in wonder
well i thought that was a pretty badass opening
line but really with the world slowly opening back
up traveling has become more and more
accessible over the past few years
thanks to the internet and so is finding
interesting destinations to experience
my name is eric conover i'm a filmmaker and
world traveler living here in new york city and
in this video i'm going to show you the top most
incredible travel destinations you have to see
to believe now i'm not pulling this footage off
the internet like some travel guides i've been
to and experienced every single destination first
hand usually i find new places to travel through
videos like this one so comment down below the
most unique place you've ever been to on earth
and without any ado these are the most incredible
travel destinations you have to see to believe
number one is norway norway is hands down the
most beautiful destination i have ever experienced
norway is a scandinavian country
encompassing vast mountains
glaciers and deep coastal fjords i recommend
going in early summer the days are long and warm
while the nights are cool and short if you
go far enough north the sun doesn't set at
all and you can experience the phenomenon known
as the midnight sun 12 30 in the morning it's june
the 11th so it's almost the first day of summer
which is the longest day of the year i haven't
been sleeping the past two days just because it
doesn't get dark it's always light out i mean
look at this the sun just dips down low enough
below the horizon where it's like a sunset for two
hours straight and then it pops right back up at
about two maybe 145 real strange but kind of cool
in norway you can do everything from
climate glacier to windsurfing on the coast
along with white water kayaking back breaking
downhill cycling and of course road trip for days
number two is bali now i know you're all thinking
everyone and their dog on instagram has been to
bali has taken photos has made videos there but
there's good reason for that bali is truly a
place to find yourself there is an energy there
unlike anywhere else i've ever been in the world
bali is an indonesian island known
for its forested volcanic mountains
iconic rice paddies beaches and coral reefs one of
the coolest things is while in bali you can stay
in a luxury villa for just about 20 us dollars
per night my number one thing to do in bali
is buy or rent a motorbike and explore the
unknown areas and the surrounding islands
sometimes you gotta go on your own adventures
i'm in full travel mode i didn't even wear shoes
oh my gosh would you look at
this head up north to ubud
and play with the monkeys
welcome to the monkey forest in ubud what's
he doing oh no that's the camera you can't
follow me i have to leave oh no you can't grab
that i'm sorry or wake up at sunrise and bathe
under a waterfall book it one way ticket the bali
and just let the journey happen number three is
the maldives if you want to get lost at sea in the
best way possible you need to head to the maldives
the maldives is a tropical nation in the indian
ocean comprised of 26 ring-shaped atolls which
are made up of more than 1 000 coral islands it's
known for its beaches blue lagoons and extensive
reefs now when you go to the maldives you have two
options for places to stay the first you pay a ton
of money and you stay in a very nice all-inclusive
resort so we're taking a boat now to the four
seasons resort we're grabbing some lunch we might
be able to explore the resort a little bit just
so we could film i guess the other side of staying
in the maldives because it is very very different
golf carts all around they were saying it
is ten thousand dollars per night for the
top room here i think doing what we're doing
on the boat is the best way to see them all
the second you travel with some friends
hire a surf boat and just island hop
there is nothing in the whole world like living
on a boat in the middle of the indian ocean early
september is a good time to visit the weather
was beautiful and the surf was very very good
and if you're not into surfing you can always
island hop and hang out with some locals
go free diving on one of the many reefs or even
find your own deserted island all to yourself
number four is japan japan is an island
nation in the pacific ocean with dense
cities mountainous national parks and thousands
of shrines and temples while traveling in japan i
opted to stay in traditional japanese inns to
fully immerse myself in the japanese culture
this japanese inn has an open-air hot spring bath
welcome to my humble abode the best way to get
around is by bullet train which is never late
or to hop on a quick flight i have a few free
hours to go off and just do whatever so i can't
come to japan and not go to a market the food
has to be hands down the most just interesting
part coming to japan there is some food that
you would never even imagine eating if you are
from the states while tokyo is an amazing city i
wanted to see the countryside i went up north to
matashima and stayed at a local fisherman's inn
i woke up the next day before sunrise and
hiked to the top of a hill to see the day begin
then i went all the way south to zamami island
which is a relatively unknown spot to westerners
and it is home to world-class diving and some of
the most remote untouched beaches on planet earth
number five is bonaire bonaire is a charming dutch
island located 50 miles north of venezuela and is
a part of the abc island chain next to aruba and
curacao far far below the hurricane bell bonaire
has perfect weather almost year round the number
one thing to do on bonaire is to scuba dive you
can scuba both in the day or for the daring scuba
diving at night this is a bucket list thing right
here i've been wanting you've never been diving
before never ever we're actually joined by a lot
of people this place is super popular just because
by the pillars that's where the fish hang out
which is one of the most terrifying exhilarating
experiences i've ever had bonaire is home to some
of the clearest blue waters on planet earth and
has some of the most lively reefs that i have ever
seen you can free dive in the freshwater limestone
cave network that runs below the island take a
drive to the pink salt pans in the south hop on
a water taxi to climb on air a tiny uninhabited
island right off the coast to do some snorkeling
home to some of the bluest waters on earth bonaire
is truly paradise number six is new york city
new york is the capital of the world and has been
my home for the past five years any time of the
year is honestly the best time to visit new york
but if i had to choose i would pick early summer
or late fall although there's no place like new
york in the winter with a little snow on the
ground new york has something for everyone
it's that place where you come to make your
dreams come true you can go enjoy the sights
like the empire state building the top of one
world trade head down to soho for some amazing
food and shopping or take in central park new
york is my favorite city in the whole world
and i think everyone should at least visit or
live in new york at least once in their life
number seven is hawaii hawaii is an isolated
volcanic island chain in the central pacific ocean
its islands are renowned for the rugged landscapes
of cliffs waterfalls and is truly one of the most
incredible places i have ever traveled to
hands down the most incredible experience
i've had in hawaii was driving up to the summit
of haleakala on maui and watching the sunset
10 000 feet above maui watching the sun go down
the sky is lit up i am so amped on life right now
and do you hear that it is absolutely
quiet up here there's not a breath of wind
there's not a single person i am so at peace right
now driving the iconic road to hana is a must
make sure to leave it very early to avoid all the
tourists and stop for some banana bread along the
way on the island of lanai go horseback riding
and off-roading on the backside of the island
through the lush tropical rainforests finally on
the island of oahu hike to the top of diamond head
at sunrise make friends with the locals and truly
experience ancient hawaiian traditions such as
pounding poi hawaii is that place that sticks out
my mind when someone asks me where is the coolest
place you've ever been and well if you made it
this far comment down below and let me know what
kind of videos you want to see on this channel
as a lot of you may have realized that video
the one you just saw that was an old post that
i've regrettably deleted off my channel i found
the hard drive realized hey i am proud of this
content and re-uploaded it for you to watch now
in whatever year you're watching so let me know
what kinds of videos from me resonate the most
with you what do you like to watch the most of
it's always good to get that temperature check
from the audience and see what the people want
to see do you want to see vlogs do you want to
see just chubby golden retrievers laying
around nap time oh tongue tattoos let me
know down below i hope you're well watching this
video and with that i'll see you in the next one